And
Amanda Seales reveals why she and Issa
Rae stopped talking on the set of
Insecure season 5.
As we started talking about the new show
that come out, Issa started reading
reading a review of the show out loud to
the group, okay? She's reading the show
out loud to the group. So, we're all
sitting there listening and we're all
commenting and involved in the
commentary and in the conversation.
Everybody as a group is talking. And
when I say everybody, I mean the cast
members. We're all chit-chatting about
it, okay?
Together. All of us together.
And she fell off from the conversation
because she was reading the rest of the
article to herself. So, then she at the
I guess when she was done reading, she
said, "Oh,
yeah, it ends with da da da da da da."
And I asked, "Oh, well, did they mention
da da da da da da?" And she said, "Why
don't you just read it yourself?"
And that was the last day.
Because I had taken so much stankness
and weirdness for the past five seasons.
And it was the last season.
And I just said, "YOU KNOW WHAT? I DON'T
GOT TO TAKE THIS NO MORE."